Okay, watch Shailes Jones, throw up a black fist real quick, and then watch Simone react.
I love us.
For anyone saying, it doesn't matter that they're black, they're just women, it does matter.
And it matters to every single one of them.
And it matters to us.
So proud of this podium, and what an important podium, right?
Brownhawk!
But all in all, I don't think it'll hit me until maybe I retire, and then look back and
see everything I've done.
But tonight, I think it was a good start.
We had an all-black podium of girls, so I thought that was amazing, black girl magic.
So hopefully it just teaches all the young girls out there that you can do anything you
put your minds to.
So keep training hard.
You go girls.